怎么了？
What's going on?
我的眼睛有点痒
My eye is a little itchy.
我的也是
Mine too. Yeah.
你的眼睛好红喔 你应该去看我的眼科医生
It's really red. You should go see my eye doctor.
理查？我才不要找你的前男友看眼睛
I'm not gonna see your ex-boyfriend.
理查…一天到晚理查个没完
That's all I hear. Richard,Richard,Richard.
打从我们开始约会以后 我想我只提过两次他的名字
Since we've dated,I've said his name twice.
那好，理查、理查
Okay. So Richard,Richard.
不是理查啦 我新找的眼科医生很棒
It's not Richard. It's this new guy. He's good.
抱歉，我不去看眼科医生
I'm sorry. I'm not going to an eye doctor.
天啊，老毛病又犯了 什么？
-Oh,God. Here we go. -What?
每次只要碰到眼睛这档事 她马上就避之唯恐不及
Anytime anything comes close to touching her eye or anyone else's...
注意看
...she,like,freaks out. Watch.
罗斯，你别闹了
Ross,come on!
好，我对我的眼睛有怪癖 麻烦别再讨论了，行吗？
I have a weird thing with my eye. Can we not talk about it?
好吧…
All right
瑞秋，还记得有首很棒的歌
Hey,Rach. You know that great song?
我、我自己和… （“我”和“眼睛”同音）
"Me,Myself and Eye."
莫妮卡，别闹啦
Monica! Come on!
有没有人想吃午餐？ 有意愿的请说…我
All those in favor of getting lunch,say,"eye."
罗斯，拜托别闹了啦
Ross! Stop it!
我有多喜欢《国王与我》？
How much did I love The King and Eye?
钱德！
Chandler!
我也是…
Me too,me too!
够了，别玩了…
Just stop it! That's enough!
你还好吧？
-You okay there,man?
是的，我真的戳到了
-Yeah. I got too excited.
本集播出：“乔伊的大好机会”
The One with Joey's Big Break
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
先走了，我要带班去公园
I gotta go. I'm taking Ben to the park.
帮我亲一下他 好，再见
-Give him a kiss for me. -All right. Bye.
再见…
Bye.
很抱歉让你们夹在中间尴尬
I'm so sorry you got caught in the middle of that.
我也不是故意这么夸张 但我真的很生他的气
I didn't mean to be so out there,but I am furious with him.
别激动
Calm down?
我在克制 但一想到那个人我就有气
I'm trying. Man,that guy can push my buttons!
你干嘛那么气他？
Why are you so mad?
我不想谈，好吗？ 只是…
-I don't wanna talk about it. -lt seems like
你想榜上有名就继续说啊
You wanna be on my list too? Keep talking.
对了，谁有看到我的黑名单？
Has anyone seen my list,by the way?
没看到，长什么样子？
No. What's it look like?
就是张纸，上头写了“罗斯” 了解
-A piece of paper and it says,"Ross." -I see.
我刚和艾斯黛讲完电话 你们猜怎么了？
I just got off the phone with Estelle. Guess what?
我要当电影主角了！
I got the lead!
你要演电影主角，太厉害了
You got the lead in a movie?
是什么电影？
What's it about?
片名是“极限速度”，超酷的
It's called Shutterspeed. It's really cool.
我在地铁遇见一个女孩 一天之内坠入情网
I meet this girl in the subway and we fall in love in,like,a day.
后来她消失无踪
And then she disappears.
但我找出了她住在哪里
But I find out where she lives.
一个老太太出来开门 我问她“贝丝在哪里？”
This old lady answers the door. I say,"Where's Betsy?"
她说“贝丝已经过世十年了”
And she says,"Betsy's been dead for 10 years."
好冷
Chilling!
最棒的是 拍片地点在拉斯维加斯外的沙漠
The best part is,we're filming in the desert outside of Vegas.
兄弟，你知道那是啥意思 对，我知道那是啥意思
-You know what that means. -I know.
自驾游，我们可以租车 我周二以前到那里就行了
Road trip! We can rent a car. I have to be there by Tuesday.
等等，我祖母过世了
Wait! My grandmother's dead.
菲比，我们也可以聊聊那件事
We can talk about that too,Phoebe.
不…我是说她的计程车
No,her cab.
她八成用不到了 你们可以开去拉斯维加斯
She probably won't be using it. Drive it to Las Vegas.
好耶，菲比，谢了
All right! Thanks!
等等…
Wait…
那我的工作怎么办？
What are we gonna do about my job?
别去了 好耶！棒！自驾游，宝贝！
Not go.Great! Road trip,baby!
你没意见吧？
Is this okay?
钱德，你不用征求我的允许…
Chandler,you don't have to ask for my permission.
同意你去 谢谢
You can go.
瑞秋，快点，要去看眼科了
Rach,we'll be late for the eye doctor.
好啦，早去早解脱
All right. Let's get this over with.
看看我做了些什么啊
Look what I did.
搞得一团乱 我得先来清理一下
I mean,look at this mess.We're gonna probably have to clean this up.
看诊时间得要重约了
I mean,we're gonna have to reschedule!
若你认为这点脏乱就会影响我 那你就错了
If you thought that this mess was gonna bother me,you are wrong!
我们走吧，眨眼姑娘
All right,let's go,Blinky.
钱德！
Chandler
“中央咖啡馆”
乔伊
Hey,Joey.
你怎么了？
What's up?
我无法决定走哪条路去拉斯维加斯
I can't decide which route to take to Vegas.
你去过不少地方吧？ 对，哪都去过
You've traveled a lot,right?Yeah,I've been around.
那我该选哪一条？ 北线还是南线？
Which route should I take? The north or the south route?
走北线途经伊利诺州 有个男人会用蜜蜂当胡子
If you take the north route,there's a man with a beard of bees.
太棒了，问题解决
Great! Problem solved!
但是走南线的话 可以看会玩井字游戏的鸡
On the south route,there's a chicken that plays tic-tac-toe.
又回到原点了
Well,back to square one.
我知道有个方法能让你做决定
I know a way that you can decide.
我会问你一连串的问题 你回答得越快越好
I'll ask you a series of questions and you answer as quickly as you can.
好！
Yes!
很好，不过先别急
Good. But wait.
开始，你先放轻松
Here we go. I want you to relax.
深呼吸一口气
Take a deep breath.
心里不要想事情
Clear your mind.
花生酱和蛋白，你喜欢哪个？ 花生酱
-Peanut butter or egg whites? -Peanut butter.
消防员和游泳选手 你比较想当哪一个？
-Be a fireman or a swimmer?
游泳选手
-Swimmer.
莫妮卡和瑞秋 你比较想跟谁上床？
-You'd sleep with Monica or Rachel?
莫妮卡…
-Monica.
我一直都以为会是瑞秋呢
I always thought it'd be Rachel.
不要想事情…
-No thinking.
领带或领巾？ 领巾
Tie or ascot? -Ascot.
南线或北线？ 北线
-North or south route? -North.
答案出现，厉害吧
Bam! There you go! Huh?
不可思议 蜜蜂胡，我来咯
That was incredible! Beard of bees here I come!
这家伙又来了
This guy again.
你好吗？
Hey,what's up?
没事，今晚想看电影吗？
Not much. Wanna see a movie tonight?
好啊，你要看什么？
What do you wanna see?
不知道…
I don't know.
我知道我们要如何决定 菲比，让他见识你的游戏
I know how to decide. Show him your game.
免了，多谢
No,thank you.
她是怎么了？
What's with her?
不知道，但我知道怎么决定了
I don't know. I know how we can decide.
我问你问题，你要很快回答 好
I'm gonna ask you questions and you answer real quick.
动作片或喜剧 你比较喜欢哪一个？
-Action or comedy?
动作片
-Action.
莫妮卡和瑞秋 你比较想跟谁上床？
Who would you rather sleep with,Monica or Rachel?
老兄，你真变态
Dude,you are sick.
抱歉，我忘了你迷恋过瑞秋
I'm sorry. I forgot you had that whole Rachel thing.
天啊，这是干嘛的？
Oh,my God. What does that thing do?
这是眼球摘除机
-An eye removal machine.
好了，我要走了 开玩笑的啦…
-I'm out of here.I'm kidding.
瑞秋，我是米勒医生 莫妮卡说你有点紧张
Rachel,I'm Dr. Miller.Monica said you were nervous.
不过别担心，不会有事的
Everything will be fine.
那就结束吧 还差一点，我们要先开始
-So we're done. -Almost,but first we gotta start.
这是青光眼测试
This is a glaucoma test.
请坐
Sit down.
好吧
Okay
把脸颊放在这里
Put your chin here.
好，眼睛会有风吹的感觉
Now,you'll feel a small puff of air in each eye.
什么？
What?
一点点的风啦，你快点！
A small puff of air. Now,come on!
开始
Here we go.
一、二、三…
One,two,three.
抱歉…好吧
I'm sorry. All right.
我这次不会动
I'm gonna stay in here this time.
好了吗？
Ready?
一、二… 抱歉
-One,two -I'm sorry.
我来抓她头好了 好
You know what? I'm gonna hold her head.
不用了 好
That's okay.
一、二… 对不起
One，two…I'm sorry.
你还年轻，应该没有青光眼
You're young. You don't have glaucoma.
太好了，很高兴认识您
So it was very,very nice to meet you,sir.
你在干嘛？你疯了不成？
What are you? Are you crazy?
好，你的左眼有些微感染
You got a small,minor infection in that left eye.
这眼药水一天点三次 连续一周你就宛如新生了
Take these drops for a week and you'll be as good as new.
我不把任何东西放进眼睛里
No,I don't put things in my eye.
那好吧，三个月后再见
We'll see you here in three months.
我到时帮你装上玻璃假眼
And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
好啦，把那死眼药水给我
Give me the damn drops!
米勒医生？
Dr. Miller?
P、E、C、F、D
P-E-C-F-D.
莫妮卡，棒极了
Very good,Monica!
你知道奖品放在哪里 我当然知道
-You know where they are. -I sure do.
你没有！
And you don't get one.
那眼药水实在是太神奇了 我的眼睛百分之百好了
You know,those eye drops are a miracle.My eye is 100 percent better.
眼药水还放在我的外套里 可恶
-They're still in my coat. -Damn!
准备好上路了没？ 好了，不过那边会有多冷？
You ready to go?How cold will it be there?
我要带外套 还是带这些毛衣就够了？
Will all these sweater vests be enough?
怎么了？ 我爱你
-What? -I love you.
真希望罗斯也能一起去 我一定会很想念他的
I wish Ross was coming with us. I'll miss him.
真是多谢你了 我才刚把那个混蛋给忘掉
Thanks. I just got that jerk out of my mind.
我们住哪里？ 电影公司招待的饭店大套房？
Is the movie putting us up in a big hotel suite?
不算是，这是独立制片的电影 没有大预算
Not really. It's an independent film.We don't have a big budget.
我想我住你房间好了
I'll stay in your room.
但等你拿到酬劳之后 你会请我住饭店大套房吧？
Once you get paid,you'll be springing for a suite.
主演电影的片酬一定不少吧？
They must be paying you a lot.
是的，“极限速度”每赚一块钱 乔伊就能分到百分之一
For every dollar Shutterspeed makes...one penny of it goes right in Joey's pocket.
所以电影赚钱你才有钱拿？
You don't get paid unless it makes money?
你不知道这电影的情节吗？
Did you not hear the plot of the movie?
“贝丝已经过世十年了”
"She's been dead for 10 years."
我就快变成百万富翁了
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我只是要来跟你们说个再见
I wanted to say goodbye.
顺便托你们帮我下个注
And to see if you guys would place a little bet for me.
20美元押黑色15号
Twenty bucks on black 15.
没问题 好
-You got it! -All right.
你记得号码吧？ 记得，黑色13号
-You remember the number,right? -Yeah,black 13.
黑色15号啦！
-Black 15!
没问题
-You got it.
再见…
-All right. Bye-bye,now. -Bye,you guys.
我去车子那里替你送行 好
I'll say bye at the car.
谁要去车子那里替我送行？
Anyone wanna say bye to me at the car?
我可以替你送行 只要你不介意我眼睛化脓
I'll say goodbye to you at the car if you don't mind the pus.
再见
See you!
等等，化脓是好现象 表示快要好了
But wait a minute. The pus is good. It means it's healing.
菲比，你在看什么？
Hey,Phoebe. What you reading?
菲比？
Phoebe
嗨
Hello?
菲比？…
Phoebe
菲比？别闹了啦
Come on!
抱歉，我不知道你在这里
Sorry,I didn't see you there.
菲比，你在生我的气吗？
Phoebe,are you mad at me or something?
我做了什么让你生气的事？
If you are,please tell me what it is I did.
你不知道，我也帮不了你 我是不知道啊
-lf you don't know,I can't help you. -I don't know.
那我也无能为力了
Well,I can't help you.
不管是什么事，我都非常抱歉
Well,whatever it is,I am very,very sorry. Okay?
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.
好吧
Okay
那我们没事了？
So we're good?
好吧
All right
那晚点见咯 好，大屁股
I'll see you later,okay?Bye,fat-ass.
够了！
All right!
菲比，你快点说 我做了什么让你这么不爽？
Will you please tell me what it is that made you so mad at me?
我不知道，我不记得了
I don't know! I don't remember!
什么叫做你不记得了？
What do you mean,you can't remember?
我太专心在生你的气 气到都忘了生气的原因
I was so focused on being mad at you,I forgot what it was I was mad about.
既然忘了，那能不能就算了？
If you can't remember,can't we just forget about this?
不行，我生你的气，这很确定
Oh,no. I am mad at you. I know that much.
但我很抱歉骂你大屁股 因为你的小屁屁很可爱
But I'm sorry about the fat-ass thing because you have a sweet,little heinie.
我开得好累，你随时准备接手
I'm getting pretty tired. You'll have to take over soon.
我们才上路半小时
We've been driving for a half-hour.
而且你都没在看路
You haven't looked at the road once.
别担心，路就是路嘛
Don't worry. It's out there.
我想我该吃午饭了 是啊
Maybe I just need lunch.
你要吃吗？我请客
You wanna eat?My treat.
那不是罗斯的钱吗？
Isn't that Ross' money?
是啊，好吧，罗斯请客
Ross' treat.
你想吃什么？ 我不知道
Where do you wanna eat?I don't know.
我知道要怎么决定了
I know how we can decide.
我问你一堆问题 你得很快回答
I'll ask you questions.And then you have to answer real fast.
不要想事情，什么都不要想 好
So clear your mind. Clear it right out. Clear it out.
我没在想事情 但心里有个小紫灯的形象
It's all clear except for this image of a small,purple lamp.
这样不碍事吧？
Is that all right if that stays in there?
应该不碍事吧…
I don't see why not. I guess.
想到什么就直接回答 好
You have to answer with the first thing that pops into your head,okay?
你宁愿太湿或太干？ 太干
-Would you rather be too wet or too dry? -Too dry.
你相不相信有鬼？ 不相信
-Do you believe in ghosts? -No.
这电影会让我翻身吗？ 不会
-Will this movie be my big break? -No.
什么？
-What?
会
-Yes.
你刚才说不会
-Dude,you said,no.
我也说了会啊
-I also said,yes.
你不觉得我这次会翻身？ 对
-This won't be my big break? -No.
难以置信
I don't believe this.
乔伊，我只是不要你期望太高
Look,I just don't want you to get your hopes up too high.
你在胡说什么？ 我是电影主角耶！
What are you talking about? I'm the lead in a movie!
那他们还不付你片酬？
They're not even paying you!
听起来都不像真的电影
This doesn't sound like a real movie!
我不需要听这种话 搞不懂你干嘛泄我的气
I don't know why you're dumping all over my big break.
乔伊，我不认为你这次能翻身
I don't think this is gonna be your big break.
所以你才来这趟？ 让我觉得自己是失败者？
Are you on this trip to make me feel like a loser?
如果是这样，那我宁愿自己去
-I'd rather be alone.
你不要我陪你去？ 你这样我不要也罢
-You don't want me here?Not if you're like this.
那好吧，下次你再问那种问题 我骗你就是了
The next time you ask me a question like that,I'll lie.
对！我不要你一起去
I don't want you on the trip.
好，无所谓… 你停车，我马上走
Why don't you pull over. I'll get out now.
好啊
Fine.
滚吧
Get out.
在桥上不能随便就停车
You can't stop on a bridge.
滚啦！ 好啦！
-Get out! -Fine!
等等…桥上没有人行道！
Wait! Wait! There's no sidewalk!
我一定会死在这里
Yeah. I'm gonna die here.
“中央咖啡馆”
好，你生我的气 是因为我发胶有怪味？
Are you mad at me because my hair gel smells?
不是
No
你生我的气 是因为我说你写字像小孩？
Because I said your handwriting is childlike?
不是，这样才特别啊
No. That made me feel precious.
我知道了 因为他老爱纠正别人文法？
Because he's always correcting people's grammar?
什么“WHOM”"WHO"的
"Whom,whom."
有时候是用“WHO”啦！
Sometimes it's "who"!
是吗？有时候是…
Yeah? Sometimes it's:
还是你玩西洋棋赢了他？ 他开始居于劣势就很孩子气
Did you beat him at a board game? He's such a baby when he loses.
好，我孩子气
Okay,I'm the baby.
住手！
Hey! Stop it!
钱德，你怎么会在这里？
What are you doing here?
乔伊在大桥上 把我赶下车
Joey kicked me out of the car on the bridge.
为什么？…
-Why?
不知道，他突然发飙
-I don't know. He went crazy.
我们在玩快问快答的游戏
We played that game where you ask questions and answer fast.
没有我在场监督 绝对不能玩那个游戏
That game should not be played without my supervision.
我不知道他干嘛气成那样
I don't know what made him mad.
我只是说他这次不会翻身
All I said was that this wouldn't be his big break...
说这部电影帮不了他
...that it wouldn't do anything for him...
说这部电影不像是真的
...and that it didn't sound real.
好啦，他该把我推下桥才对
Okay,he should've pushed me off the bridge.
你袋子里有什么？
What's in the bag?
我猜想你们大家也会对我不爽
I figured you'd be mad at me...
所以我在路边检了些礼物
...so I got gifts that I found on the roadside.
谁要一条腿的泰迪熊？ 我要
-Who wants the one-legged teddy bear? -I do!
来了
Okay
差远了
-Not even close.
好啦，你帮我，我没办法
-I need help! I can't do this.
来，我帮你
Come on. Let's do it.
坐下 好
Sit down. All right,
头往后仰 好
put your head back.
把眼睛张开 好，张开了
-Now open your eyes. -Okay,they are.
我举了几只手指头？ 四只
-How many fingers am I holding up? -Four.
天啊，我心里想的也是四只
I was thinking four.
真的？ 是啊
-Really? -Yes!
这样吧，我们先来预演一次 好
Why don't we start with a practice one.
不滴眼药水 太好了
-No drops. -Great!
数到三，一、二、三…
On three. One,two,three.
你害我沙发枕都湿了
My pillow's all wet!
你自己说是预演的
Well,you said it was practice!
那你干嘛动？ 因为我知道你会骗我
Why did you move?I knew you were lying!
好吧，过来 你要干嘛？
-Come here. -What are you doing?
莫妮卡，天啊！住手！…
Stop it! Oh,my God!
我要…转回来！
I am going....Turn it over!
我要把眼药水…滴进你眼睛
I am going to get...get these drops in your eye.
天啊，你蛮力真大
Oh,my God! You really are freakishly strong.
莫妮卡，住手！…
Stop! Stop!Stop it!
可恶，空了！
Damn,it's empty!
如果现在乔伊和钱德走进来 我们就走运了
If Joey and Chandler walked in now,we could make a fortune.
一定是钱德、乔伊或罗斯
That is definitely Chandler,Joey or Ross.
或是瑞秋
Or Rachel.
喂？…
Hello
是乔伊
It's Joey.
真高兴你打来 钱德都说了，他很难过
Chandler told me what happened. He's really upset.
等他知道他毛衣的下场 他一定会更难过
Not as upset as he'll be when he finds out what I did with his sweater vests.
你把他的毛衣怎么了？
What did you do to them?
这么说吧，在俄亥俄州 有一伙打扮亮丽的狗
There's a well-dressed pack of dogs in Ohio.
莫妮卡？菲比在吗？ 我有车子的事要问她
I gotta ask Phoebe something about the car.
她在，你等等
Hold on one second.
嗨 嗨，菲比，你听我说
-Hey,dude. -Hey,Phoebe.
座位底下有个木盒滑出来 那是什么？
This wooden box keeps sliding out. What is it?
那是我祖母
My grandma.
乔伊，谢谢你，她玩得很愉快
And thanks. She's having a great time.
是乔伊吗？我要跟他说…
Is that Joey? Let me talk to him.
乔伊？钱德不知道你…
Chandler's here. He was wondering if
我想他零钱正好用完了
I guess he ran out of change.
他连话都不想跟我说 这样我要怎么跟他道歉？
How am I gonna apologize to him if he won't even talk to me?
或许你应该寄点东西给他
Send him something.
等他到了拉斯维加斯 就知道你想表达歉意了
So when he gets there,he'll know you're sorry.
好主意，上哪儿找一堆A片？
That's a good idea. I wonder where I could get a basket of porn?
不行，不能用A片道歉啦 真的？
No,don't say,"I'm sorry," with porn.
你应该寄一条烟过去 他可以用来换取保护
You should send him a carton of cigarettes.Because that way he can trade it for protection.
错了，监狱里才是这样
No. That's prison.
菲比，我知道要怎么找出原因
I know how we're gonna figure this out.
好，什么都不要想
Clear your mind...
想到什么就直接回答
...and answer the first thing that comes into your head.
好吗？
Okay？
你比较喜欢植物还是动物？ 动物
-Do you like flora or fauna? -Fauna.
你想当西蒙还是葛芬柯（六十年代民谣歌手组合）？ 葛芬柯
-Simon or Garfunkel? -Garfunkel.
你为何生我的气？ 因为你说我很无趣
-Why are you mad? -You said I was boring.
我何时说过你无趣了？
When did I say that?
天啊，我想起来了 我们下西洋棋那次
Oh,my God! I remember now! We were playing chess.
菲比，我和你没下过西洋棋
Phoebe,you and l have never played chess.
有啦，记得冰冻湖那次吗？ 我们玩西洋棋，你说我很无趣
Remember that time on the frozen lake? We were playing. You said I was boring.
然后你脱下面具 变成了卡梅隆迪亚兹（女影星）
Then you took off your energy mask and you were Cameron Diaz.
好吧，这有可能是梦境
There's a chance this may have been a dream.
所以你这阵子以来对我不爽 全是因为一场梦？
So this entire time,you've been angry with me because of a dream?
菲比，现在轮到我对你不爽了
Well,guess what,now I'm mad at you.
我想确定这次不是作梦 否则我们是在浪费彼此的时间
I wanted to make sure this wasn't a dream.Otherwise we're wasting our time.
史丹利！
Stanley!
你的主角来了，咱们开工吧
Your leading man is here. Let's get to work.
计划有些改变，我们停拍了
Slight change of plans.We've shut down.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
钱的原因，我们没钱
It's a money thing. We don't have any.
你在开玩笑吧？ 不是
You're kidding,right?
什么？
What?
这或许只是暂时的
It's probably just temporary.
我们希望能快点筹到资金 你先撑一下
We're hoping to get some money soon. Just hang out.
撑一下？要撑多久？
Hang out? How long?
不知道，一、两个星期吧
I don't know. A week. Maybe two.
资金会出现的 大家都爱投资拍片
The money will turn up.People always wanna invest in movies.
你该不会是有钱人吧？ 我不是
You're not rich?
问一下也无妨
Worth a shot.
乔伊，让我知道你在哪儿落脚
Well,Joey,let me know where you're staying,okay?
你是乔伊崔比亚尼吗？ 我是
Hey,pal. Are you Joey Tribbiani?
这是有人留给你的 谢了
These got left for you.Thanks.
恭喜你翻身了
"Congratulations on your big break."
喂？
Hello
莫妮卡，我是乔伊
-Monica,it's Joey. -Hey,Joey.
你当了大明星还是记得我
You remember me even though you're a star.
得了吧，忘记你也要好几年
Come on. It'll be years before I forget you.
拍片现场是什么样子？
What's it like on a movie set?
你有自己的更衣室吗？ 有专属的私人座椅吗？
Do you have a dressing room and a chair with your name?
有啊，一切都在进行当中
Yeah,yeah,I got all that going on.
你一定要跟钱德说 他完完全全看走眼了
Tell Chandler he couldn't have been more wrong.
莫妮卡，我得挂了 我的寿司送来了
I gotta go,Monica. My sushi's here.
抱歉，多谢你们等我 没关系
Sorry about that. Thanks for waiting.
大家笑一个，多谢
Everybody smile.Thanks a lot.
在凯萨酒店住得愉快 祝你们“罗马”很棒（乔伊自己造的词）
Enjoy your stay at Caesars. We hope it's toga-rific.
杀了我吧…
Kill me. Kill me now.
瑞秋，电视指南递给我好吗？ 好啊
Rach,can you pass me the TV Guide?
上！
Go!
住手！…天啊！
What are you doing? Get off! Oh,my God!
好了…
Hold it open. Okay.
三、四个小时后再见
We'll see you in about three or four hours.